<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analysis on Academic</title>
    <link>/tags/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analysis on Academic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 21:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Health and Economic Impact of Storms and Severe Weather Events</title>
      <link>/post/2018-09-02-reproducible-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-09-02-reproducible-research/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis In this analysis I amd concerned with two primary points. Which event types have the greatest health impact and the greatest economic impact. I begin my work with data processing to create usable objects for results visualization. I finish my analysis with two plots and a final table.
 Package Load Load packages required for analysis.
require(tidyverse) require(lubridate) require(kableExtra)  Data Import Leveraging read_csv from the readr packackge included with tidyverse to import the dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Pay-As-You-Throw (PAYT) Cost Recovery Rate</title>
      <link>/post/2017-11-20-payt-estimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-11-20-payt-estimate/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As a different approach to this exercise, I would like to avoid traditional Microsoft Excel analysis and deliver my product in a fully reproducible R Markdown format. I will attempt to walk you through my thought process in a simple fashion, including all code chunks and formulas. If this analysis is consistent with a best practice approach, it can be made available to others for reproduction. The transparency and reproducibility of R Markdown allows for others to easily understand, critique and augment the analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>